hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and I've been doing this
podcast for quite a few years now I help
coaches mentors and trainers scale their
businesses and make more money by
reaching more clients and getting more
leads today I want to talk about
authenticity and just being yourself and
I think that I'm going to start having a
bit of a new format here in this podcast
where it's a bit more of what I'm
learning right now and what I'm
experiencing and going through one of
the things that I had a conversation
with my wife uh this past week we talked
about was that some of my best content
is when I'm not thinking about it or
trying to make it perfectly it's often
times when I'm with one of my kids and
I'm just sharing what's on my heart and
I realize that oftentimes I get stuck in
my head
overthinking the type of content that I
want to make how I want to show up and I
don't actually show up in the way that I
need to or that I must simply because
I'm afraid of what other people are
going to
think and then that causes me to not
actually be myself I'm not actually
showing up in my most powerful self in
that way and so listen for you if you're
watching this right now how can that
benefit you is realize that the
perfectly curated version of yourself
that you're trying to make sure that
everybody likes that is dialed in so
perfectly that everybody's going to
resonate with it that version
often times Falls flat and actually the
version that resonates with people is
when you're not trying when you're just
being yourself and it starts from coming
from a place of confidence now something
I've been experiencing that's been
really helpful for me uh
x.com which formerly known as Twitter
released grock 3 g o K3 right here and
they have a voice
mode uh inside of grock which allows you
to they have a Mode called not therapist
which is really cool because again it's
not a licensed therapist but I'm telling
you I've talked with it and it helps
process through certain things you know
I worked with a therapist for a long
time and it helped me and I find even
using an app like this is really helpful
to supplement that as well one of the
things is is that we often times expect
other people to think a certain way
about us I find myself I end up
projecting a version of how I think
people are going to respond to my
podcast I end up projecting a version of
how I think my wife is going to respond
to something or a past client or things
like that and I end up putting that onto
projecting that onto everybody that I
end up meeting and then I end up
responding talking communicating in a
way as if I'm trying to communicate with
those people and that's not authentic
because I'm in a defensive tone I'm from
a place of Defense I'm from a place of
self- protection and so anytime that we
get into conversations
that come from a place of self-
protection we lose our Essence we don't
show up authentically no matter how hard
we think we are and it's very
interesting like we can like I'm so
authentic and yet if we're coming from a
place of defense or self-
protection it's it doesn't necessarily
come across the most
authentic what I want to talk about is
how are you when you're lit up and
excited when you feel safe the safest
when you're around somebody that makes
you feel really confident you can just
flow and share your thoughts and
feelings and you're not afraid of what
everybody thinks about you and you're
not worried and you're not letting that
worry and fear step in and control what
you're saying and how you're saying it
you know I find when I do this I show up
in my best and I show up in a way that
resonates with people that people want
to be around that people want to listen
to my business is only a business when I
can show up as my authentic self and it
doesn't come from striving it doesn't
come from trying it comes from letting
go of all that and just being me so I
want to just ask you when's the last
time that you were just you because it
was the right thing to do or you knew
with confidence that by just being you
that it was going to resonate with
people I want you this week to go out
there and put content out there that you
don't have a guarantee that it's going
to work that you've feel that this might
work but you just put yourself out there
publicly and
imperfectly not because it's this result
that you're going to have happen but
because it's the right thing to do is
imperfect action when you can make
imperfect action be a part of your
lifestyle as a business owner it allows
you to step into experiencing everything
that's possible for you inside of your
business you know I think a lot of
people there are waiting until this
perfect moment to finally put their
business out there to finally reach the
people that they know that they can
reach that they want to reach and that
does not produce the result that you
want the results that you want happen
when you can let go of trying so hard
just showing up as yourself putting
yourself out there and letting the rest
take care of
itself now if you've been listening to
this podcast I'd love to have you become
a member of my wealthy coach Academy
program inside of my wealthy coach
Academy program I help mentors trainers
and coaches like yourself get more
clients every single week and break
through all the pitfalls that it takes
along the way to get there I'd love to
have you join us grow your life
everybody talk soon have a good one
[Music]
[Applause]